Guide to the Anthony Barboza papers, ca. 1970-1999.
Barboza, Anthony papers
- Posters
  - Camille Billops Minstrel Series - "Old Black Joe" Poster, 1991 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
  - Black Musicians Catalog, Inc. Poster, 1970 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
  - Saheb Sarbib and Hamiet Bluiett signed poster, December 11, 1982 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
    NYU Program Board New Music Showcase
  - International Exhibition of Photography and Related Visual Arts Poster, 1997 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
  - Macy's Special Events Poster (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
    Kamoinge Photographers
  - Henry Threadgill Sextet Poster (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
    S.O.B.'s Salutes Jazz! New York Only Appearance
  - Izithombe Poster - Harlem, N.Y., photo by Klytus Smith, 1962 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
  - Izithombe Poster - Malcolm X and Ralph Cooper, photo by Klytus Smith, 1964 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Painting (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
  - Ottis Anderson on Teamwork Poster (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
  - Bart Oates on Working Together Poster (Map-case Z-19, Folder 2)
  - Jazz Selects: Photos by Anthony Barboza, Exhibit Poster (Map-case Z-19, Folder 3)
  - Jazz Musicians of the 80s Poster (Map-case Z-19, Folder 3)
  - World Heavyweight Champion Holyfield Tyson - Poster, 1991 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 4)
  - George Jackson - Soledad Brother Poster, 1971 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 4)
  - CB4 - The Movie Poster, 1992 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 4)
  - Just Another Girl on the I.R.T. Poster (Map-case Z-19, Folder 4)
- Documents
  - Aetna African American History Calendar, 1998-2000 (Box 27)
    "The Story of Fitness," "The Gift of Giving Back," "Leaders of the Century"
  - Amiri Baraka Press Release (Box 27)
  - "Exposure - Ten Photographers' Work." By Creative Artists Public Service Program (Box 27)
  - Ntozake Shange - "The Sweet Breath of Life" (Box 27)
    With Photographs by Kamoinge, Inc.
  - Blue Note Poster, 1984 (Box 27)
  - "Outtakes" - The Publication by Photographers for Photographers and their Friends, Fall 1992 (Box 27)
    Issue 1. Featuring photography by Anthony Barboza
  - Seagram's Gin Ad (Box 27)
    Featuring photograph of Geoffrey Holder
  - "Whitewall Magazine" - Summer 2010 issue containing interview with Anthony Barboza (page74), 2010 (Box 27)
  - AIR - Articles and Papers, 1978-1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Articles, 1983-2009 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Anthony Barboza Interview, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - "Black Borders," book by Anthony Barboza, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Blue Note Papers, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Buttons (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Correspondences, 1995-2000 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Interviews (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Pheeroan Aklaff, Big Nick Nicholas, Hamiett Bluiett, Arthur Blythe, Lester Bowie, Betty Carter, Olu Dara
  - Interviews (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Craig Harris, Jay Hoggard, Fred Hopkins, Joseph Jarman, Leroy Jenkins, Steve McCall, Butch Morris, Oliver Lake
  - Interviews (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Deidre Murray, Donald Pullen, Saheb Sarbib, Cecil Taylor, Henry Threadgill, Cassandra Wilson, Philip Wilson
  - Jazz Musicians - Miscellaneous Info (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Job Sheets, 1994-2004 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Kamoinge, 1970s (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Magazines (Box 32, Folder 14-16)
  - Mailings and Pamphlets (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Books, Pamphlets, Postcards (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Misc. Papers (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Papers, Correspondences (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Pamphlets and Booklets (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Pamphlets, Booklets, and Posters (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - The New School Jazz and Contemporary Music Program (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Newsletters and Pamphlets, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Printed Photographs (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Promotional Materials (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Henry Threadgill Articles and Papers (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Caetano Veloso Info and Articles (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Rasa Artists Book (Box 32)
    Management, booking and consultation firm. Sam Rivers, Leroy Jenkins, Anthony Braxton,
    Art Ensemble of Chicago, Leo Smith's New Dalta Ahkri, Joe Henderson, Chico Freeman,
    George Lewis, Sonny Fortune, Hal Galper, Oliver Lake, Miroslav Vitous, World Saxophone Quartet
  - Job Sheets, 1992-2005 (Box 33, Folder 1-5)
- Audio Recordings
  - Memories Thru Vision, 1936-1979; TR-8324 (Box 28)
  - Pheeroan Aklaff, December 4, 1984; TR-9367 (Box 28)
  - Benny Andrews, TR-9368 (Box 28)
    Interview with Anthony Barboza
  - Anthony Barboza - Speech, April 6, 2009; TR-9369 (Box 28)
  - Anthony Barboza - Lecture at Rochester Institute of Technology, March 21, 1991; TR-9370 (Box 28)
  - Anthony Barboza - Comments on Photograph Shootings, 1991; TR-9371 (Box 28)
    With Hoten Calisher, Walter Abish, E.L. Doctorow
  - Big Nick Nicholas Interview, February 16, 1984; TR-9372 (Box 28)
  - Hamiett Bluiett Interview, December 22, 1983; TR-9373 (Box 28)
  - Arthur Blythe Interview, February 3, 1984; TR-9374 (Box 28)
  - Lester Bowie Interview, March 12, 1984; TR-9375 (Box 28)
  - Betty Carter Interview, February 21, 1984; TR-9376 (Box 28)
  - James Carter, TR-9377 (Box 28)
  - Olu Dara Interview, February 4, 1984; TR-9378 (Box 28)
  - Roy Eldridge and the Swing Trumpets, TR-9379 (Box 28)
  - Roy Eldridge and the Swing Trumpets - The Essential Keynote Collection Vol. 4, TR-9380 (Box 28)
  - Chico Freeman - Tales of Ellington, April 5, 1987; TR-9381 (Box 28)
  - Chico Freeman - The Emissary, 1996; TR-9382 (Box 28)
  - Chico Hamilton - Dancing to a Different Drummer, TR-9383 (Box 28)
  - Craig Harris Interview, December 20, 1983; TR-9384 (Box 28)
  - Craig Harris and Henry Threadgill at Photo Show Opening, January 13, 1990; TR-9385 (Box 28)
  - Blanchard Harrison, 1986; TR-9386 (Box 28)
  - John Hicks Interview, April 6, 1984; TR-9387 (Box 28)
  - Jay Hoggard Interview, November 18, 1983; TR-9388 (Box 28)
  - Fred Hopkins Interview, December 21, 1983; TR-9389 (Box 28)
  - Oliver Lake Interview, February 3, 1984; TR-9390 (Box 28)
  - Leroy Jenkins Interview, April 23, 1984; TR-9391 (Box 28)
  - Steve McCall Interview, March 16, 1984; TR-9392 (Box 28)
  - Thelonious Monk, TR-9393 (Box 28)
  - Butch Morris Interview, April 20, 1984; TR-9394 (Box 28)
  - Don Moye Interview, June 29, 1984; TR-9395 (Box 28)
  - Diedre Murray Interview, July 16, 1984; TR-9396 (Box 28)
  - Don Pullen Interview, September 12, 1984; TR-9397 (Box 28)
  - Saheb Sarbib Interview, October 20, 1983; TR-9398 (Box 28)
  - Stringology, September 1983; TR-9399 (Box 28)
  - Cecil Taylor Interview Parts 1 and 2, September 4, 1984; TR-9400 (Box 28)
  - Cecil Taylor Interview Part 3, September 4, 1984; TR-9401 (Box 28)
  - Henry Threadgill Interview, October 15, 1983; TR-9402 (Box 29)
  - Henry Threadgill - Makin' A Move, September 14, 1997; TR-9403 (Box 29)
  - Shawn Walker Interview, July 28, 1987; TR-9404 (Box 29)
  - Cassandra Wilson Interview, June 20, 1984; TR-9405 (Box 29)
  - Philip Wilson Interview, April 16, 1984; TR-9406 (Box 29)
  - "No. 1 Smooth Jazz Hits!", 2006; 1852 (Box 29)
  - "No. 1 Smooth Jazz Radio Hits", 2004; 1853 (Box 29)
  - "Smooth Jazz - Quiet Storm Slow Jams", 2007; 1854 (Box 29)
  - "Smooth Jazz - Sax at Midnight", 2003; 1855 (Box 29)
  - "Street Wize - Sexy Love", 2007; 1856 (Box 29)
  - "Touch Me In The Morning - Smooth Jazz Plays The Greatest Love Songs From Back In The day", 2005; 1857 (Box 29)
  - Kim Waters - "All For Love", 2005; 1858 (Box 29)
  - Pamela Williams - "The Look Of Love", 2007; 1859 (Box 29)
  - Barboza Shooting Joseph Heller, Easthampton, NY, January 15, 1998; V-6038 (Box 29)
  - Miles Davis TV Commercial, 1984; V-6039 (Box 29)
  - Gene Ammons - "Greatest Hits", 1974; SR-1229 (Box 30)
  - Joan Armatrading - "Secret Secrets", 1985; SR-1230 (Box 30)
  - Ashford and Simpson - "Solid", 1984; SR-1231 (Box 30)
  - Patti Austin - "End of the Rainbow", 1976; SR-1232 (Box 30)
  - Art Blakey and the Jazz Messengers - "Soul Finger", 1965; SR-1233 (Box 30)
  - The Blue Velvets - "Changes", 1979; SR-1234 (Box 30)
  - Chaka Khan - "Naughty", 1980; SR-1235 (Box 30)
  - Ray Charles - "Ain't It So", 1979; SR-1236 (Box 30)
  - Codona - "Codona 2", 1981; SR-1237 (Box 30)
    Collin Walcott, Don Cherry, Nana Vasconcelos
  - Codona - "Codona 3", 1983; SR-1238 (Box 30)
  - Ornette Coleman and Prime Time - "Virgin Beauty", 1988; SR-1239 (Box 30)
  - Alice Coltrane - "Journey in Satchidananda", 1971; SR-1240 (Box 30)
    Featuring Pharoah Sanders
  - "Blues for Coltrane: A Tribute to John Coltrane", 1988; SR-1241 (Box 30)
    Featuring McCoy Tyner, Pharoah Sanders, David Murray, Cecil McBee, Roy Haynes
  - Commodores - "Nightshift", 1984; SR-1242 (Box 30)
  - Commodores - "Nightshift", 1984-1985; SR-1243 (Box 30)
  - Jack DeJohnette - "Special Edition", 1980; SR-1244 (Box 30)
  - Eric B and Rakim - "Paid In Full", 1987; SR-1245 (Box 30)
  - "Flashdance: Original Soundtrack from the Motion Picture", 1983; SR-1246 (Box 30)
  - Coleman Hawkins - "Bean and the Boys", 1944-1949; SR-1247 (Box 30)
    Fats Navarro, J.J. Johnson, Milt Jackson, Thelonious Monk, Hank Jones, Max Roach, Kenny Clarke, and others
  - The Heath Brothers - "Marchin' On", 1976; SR-1248 (Box 30)
    Albert, Jimmy, and Percy, featuring Stanley Cowell
  - Nona Hendryx - "Nona Hendryx", 1977; SR-1249 (Box 30)
  - Freddie Jackson - "Rock Me Tonight", 1985; SR-1250 (Box 30)
  - Keith Jarrett - "The Celestial Hawk", 1980; SR-1251 (Box 30)
  - Jesse Johnson - "Jesse Johnson's Revue", 1985; SR-1252 (Box 30)
  - Earl Klugh - "Earl Klugh", 1976; SR-1253 (Box 30)
  - Patti Labelle - "Tasty", 1978; SR-1254 (Box 30)
  - Ramsey Lewis - "The Best of Ramsey Lewis", 1972; SR-1255 (Box 30)
  - Lisa Lisa and Cult Jam - "Lisa Lisa and Cult Jam With Full Force", 1985; SR-1256 (Box 30)
  - "Live At Newport", 1984; SR-1257 (Box 30)
    Muddy Waters, B.B. King, and Big Mama Thorton
  - Tania Maria - "Taurus", 1982; SR-1258 (Box 30)
  - Brandford Marsalis - "Renaissance", 1987; SR-1259 (Box 30)
  - Brandford Marsalis - "Random Abstract", 1988; SR-1260 (Box 30)
  - Harvey Mason - "Groovin' You", 1979; SR-1261 (Box 30)
  - Jackie McLean - "Capuchin Swing", 1960; SR-1262 (Box 30)
  - Jackie McLean - "Jackie's Bag", 1959-1960; SR-1263 (Box 30)
  - Jackie McLean - "Let Freedom Ring", 1962; SR-1264 (Box 30)
  - Jackie McLean - "Right Now", 1965; SR-1265 (Box 30)
  - Jackie McLean - "Demon's Dance", 1967; SR-1266 (Box 30)
  - Jackie McLean - "A Ghetto Lullaby", 1974; SR-1267 (Box 30)
  - Jackie McLean - "Monuments", 1979; SR-1268 (Box 30)
  - Jackie McLean and Michael Carvin- "Antiquity", 1975; SR-1269 (Box 30)
  - The Mighty Clouds of Joy - "Truth Is The Power", 1977; SR-1270 (Box 31)
  - Charlie Mingus - "Blues and Roots", 1960; SR-1271 (Box 31)
  - Mongo Santa Maria - "Mongomania", 1967; SR-1272 (Box 31)
  - Thelonious Monk - "Misterioso", 1965; SR-1273 (Box 31)
  - Thelonious Monk - "Brilliance", 1976; SR-1274 (Box 31)
  - Wes Montgomery - "The Best of Wes Montgomery", 1967; SR-1275 (Box 31)
  - The Moonglows - "The Return of the Moonglows", 1972; SR-1276 (Box 31)
  - James Newton - "In Venice", 1988; SR-1277 (Box 31)
  - "One Night With Blue Note - Preserved", February 22, 1985; SR-1278 (Box 31)
    The Entire Blue Note Concert - A Four Record Set
  - Minnie Riperton - "Perfect Angel", 1974; SR-1279 (Box 31)
  - Rahsaan Roland Kirk - "Bright Moments", 1973; SR-1280 (Box 31)
  - Rahsaan Roland Kirk - "The Return of the 5000 lb. Man", 1975; SR-1281 (Box 31)
  - Rahsaan Roland Kirk - "Kirkatron", 1977; SR-1282 (Box 31)
  - The Ramsey Lewis Trio - "The In Crowd", 1965; SR-1283 (Box 31)
  - The Ramsey Lewis Trio - "Upendo Ni Pamoja", 1972; SR-1284 (Box 31)
  - Max Roach Double Quartet - "Easy Winners", 1985; SR-1285 (Box 31)
  - Sonny Rollins - "East Broadway Run Down", 1966; SR-1286 (Box 31)
  - "Round Midnight - Original Motion Picture Soundtrack", 1986; SR-1287 (Box 31)
  - Pharoah Sanders - "Tauhid", 1966; SR-1288 (Box 31)
  - Sheila E. - "The Glamorous Life", 1984; SR-1289 (Box 31)
  - Steel Pulse - "Babylon The Bandit", 1985; SR-1290 (Box 31)
  - Steppenwolf - "Steppenwolf", 1968; SR-1291 (Box 31)
  - Art Tatum - "Piano Starts Here", 1987; SR-1292 (Box 31)
  - Cecil Taylor - "Indent", 1973; SR-1293 (Box 31)
  - Cecil Taylor - "Live in the Black Forest", 1979; SR-1294 (Box 31)
  - The Time - "The Time", 1981; SR-1295 (Box 31)
  - Yardbrough and Peoples - "Be A Winner", 1984; SR-1296 (Box 31)
  - Zulena - "Z-licious", 1978; SR-1297 (Box 31)